Iginari expedition!
I'm Yasumori Waka.
I'm Kichise Shinju.
please remember me
We are the Iginari explorers!
Yasumori-san and Shinju-san today.
A little bit for both of us today.
You know what I mean when I think of these two.
We have a plan.
Candy?
No, sir.
What did you do with the candy?
I was writing something.
Or writing.
Also, we used to do that sewing thing, didn't we?
You did it. One more time.
Speaking of design, these two are... well... artists.
So today's exploration is
Design a T-shirt to wear at the Inari Tohoku Aquarium! Wow!
On the 20th and 21st of April, we will be holding an exhibition at the Sendai Umi-no-Mori Aquarium called "Inari Tohoku Aquarium".
See you there!
This is one of the Endo Chain's 95th anniversary events, and Endo Chain will be hosting the event.
For those two days, everyone from Tohoku-san, the two of us who were MC's, and the staff members wore uniforms, and we were all very happy to be there.
The T-shirt, the poster you're holding right now, is this what you call the main visual?
You two are in the picture, aren't you? I'm sorry, I'm sorry! Here they are!
No, it's not! I made a mistake!
That's good!
No! Why, why, why?
Stop it! You're not supposed to be watching me, are you?
No, no, no! Don't answer it!
What a great big sister!
Hey! You've become so charming!
And? I am this!
Why are you both lying?
Since when? This is it!
Oh, that's nice! The fishing is amazing!
The fishing has been great! Why are you looking in the wrong place?
What the hell? Marriage?
Are you going to do it? Marriage failure!
Oh, my goodness! I'm embarrassed! It's good to give an honest compliment!
They are cute! They are all cute!
The aquarium is suddenly far away from the aquarium.
The 20th is an event at Umi-no-Mori Aquarium, the 21st is an event at E-Beans, and the
I'm going to wear the t-shirt there for two days.
Yes, two days.
That could be Ronty, I don't know.
Please don't come stuffing that area, here and now.
I've already asked so many questions.
Design it anyway.
It's over.
Now let's get to the design.
Yes, sir.
Let's get started on the design!
I checked and it's just a T-shirt.
The two of us work together to create the design.
It could be split front and back.
Let's talk about putting something like this in.
We decided to make it.
You can put your logo on something like this, right?
It looks like you can put your logo on it.
This is, you know, you want to put your logo on it, don't you?
Yeah, I want to put it in.
Where do I put it?
The most common ones are around here and there.
hello (on phone, replying to "moshimoshi")
Cuffs.
Shin-san, you can go further.
without reserve
Like, let's leave the design to Yasumori-san.
There's something in the air like that from the beginning.
Are you a yes-man? Hey, hey, hey, hey.
I've always been that way.
Let's let Pearl have the final say today.
Please, Daisen.
Okay, so first of all, I've taken your opinions into account.
Oh, I put a summary out.
I think it's easier to draw a design if it's in an easily visible place.
If it gets to be here, I'll paint both the front and the back.
It's going to be hard.
Then let's put it in here. Quick!
On your back! On your back, like, right here.
YES, but in the end.
Is there any place you can put Shinge-san? Opinion
Now that's just one opinion of Yasumori's.
But now, you know, you can put it on your back, for example, or you can put your name on it.
certainly
ivory-boxing
Oh, that's so nice.
I'm trying to put in affordable right or something.
very good idea
If you put this in your sleeve...
Oh, no! You can wear this on your sleeve.
That's nice. That's cute. And I'll take a T-shirt with this on the back.
I mean, you can put it in here, right? Once you've written the T-shirt, you're nervous.
Can we put the logo here? Yeah, okay. Is that the back? Yes, the back.
Yes Logo Like this
So we just need to decide between here and the front design. OK.
So would you rather be in charge of the back or the front? Back.
What do you think of the fast bites?
No, well, well, well, well, but this is a big responsibility, really.
That's right. I didn't take this picture because I thought it would be easy. I'll leave it to you because you're different and really trustworthy.
But I've thought about it before, and I'd like your opinion on what you'd like to see in Pearl's design.
I hope you can incorporate that into your own. That's good, that's good, that's good.
I understand... I really did put out a kitchen car for Tohokusan, but...
Waka-san came up with the logo and all that, so as expected, I can count on you.
I'm an artistic person, but... well, I went to high school for two years.
I was an art major, and I've been showing it in my expedition videos, and I've been showing it all along.
That's why, after all, this is the place to go for peace of mind and peace of mind.
It's a logo, right? You're taking up a lot of space with the logo.
You don't write much?
Write on this page or something.
Like, I'm asking for this here.
You can write it in shiji
It's going to be tiny, isn't it?
For example, let's take the illustration I just wrote as (1).
Like (1) here.
The balance will be written.
Detail 1) over here.
oh, yes!
It's a little bit like your opinion was Shinju-san's opinion.
Just a suggestion there.
So, first of all, here's a rough sketch, and there's the table of composition.
By writing the details like this, it is very easy for the creator to understand.
I see. I should probably do that.
That's what I'm talking about.
That's not true.
How do you feel now?
feeling good
Omoro!
Let's do it!
I wish I could put my name on it.
Tohokusan, member's name?
I think it's good.
Names of Syndepont members
Would you rather be a dolphin or a penguin?
I have an image of a dolphin, though.
isn't it?
You're good, your handwriting.
Really?
You did?
I didn't do it.
You're good at it!
What? He's giving me so many compliments today.
It's not a huge compliment.
What? Parent-child theory?
Does this look like a dolphin headdress?
be awfully clear
Then it's like this.
Nine members wearing dolphin headgear.
They're so good! They're so good! Really?
I love that kind of thing!
And the color of the headgear came from the members? Yes, they did.
Oh my God, it's so authentic!
It's too good to be true, but if I'm going to go to the trouble of making something, I've got to make it pretty.
Sure, I really love those costumes. I'm looking forward to them.
It's wonderful that you've already come up with this in about 5 minutes after you started designing.
I think I'll write it in hiragana.
I've seen English before.
I've never seen hiragana either.
Indeed.
I know, right?
Rune-chan Rene
What is Yuna's mouth?
Raimage.
You've even changed the shape of your face properly.
that's true
More than the same.
easy to understand
Easy to understand?
I'm in this bed.
yeah
Mon-chan or winking at you?
It might be cute, sure.
I, uh...
I want to sleep.
Do you want to sleep?
I want it to be one of these.
OK, OK
Just draw the members' faces like this.
OK Plan is complete
Yes, sir.
Make the logo about this much.
So maybe I can illustrate something around here.
It would be nice if there were.
I know, right?
Illustration of what you would like to see.
Before, Yasumori drew these characters for us, dolphins.
grunting and groaning
Back there, it's different. It's more of an animal thing, like penguins or something.
I think it's kind of cute. Pearl thinks it's an aquarium there.
Yes, yes, yes, yes. Copy that.
Penguin. Nice.
I put my name here, but I hope that's okay.
Or if you don't draw it, it's going to feel like Hafen's.
No, it's easy to understand with the name.
Let's get rid of this name and see what we can put in.
But you can hold it back, right? I don't know.
yeah
I'll make sure to put Shimada-san and Kimitaka-san's names here, too.
Oh, sure.
Can you let me in?
All right.
Thank you.
Okay, this one here, and this one here.
That's why I added hiragana just now.
And is that it? A little illustration at the bottom.
Yes Illustration
Can you draw a penguin?
What's it like to be a penguin?
How can you paint without looking?
All right.
Like this?
Looks like an octopus wiener.
He's adorable.
Octopus wiener
cute
I don't know if this is how it's supposed to be.
(after the -te form of a verb) I want (you) to
I want a Lego block of this.
happy
whee
Your eyes are so bright.
Yes.
Evolutionary process
Is there anything else you would like me to include?
It's got some kind of saying on it.
What stories you and the aquarium have to tell.
Great.
Good! On the side of the face.
It's pretty much a joke.
very cute
cute
It's so funny to write such a saying on such a cute girl.
It's so nice! I really want one!
It's really good! It's really good! I'm so happy!
The quality is so high! It looks like it could be made into merchandise!
That's something, isn't it? I want to say something romantic like that.
Hey, I'd like to say something, but I can't think of anything at all.
what is it?
I wonder, what is it?
Romantic.
Yes, what is it?
My happiness is carried by my sea friends
That's what I'm talking about, Romanchest.
Eh, this could be difficult.
It comes out because that's what I usually think about, this.
(esp. of men) one's prime (approx. age 30)
It's something that exists.
In Yasumori's mind, absolutely.
Yes, absolutely.
not a chance
I don't usually serve that kind of thing.
(esp. of men) one's prime (approx. age 30)
My happiness is carried by my sea friends
Oh, no. Let's not do that. It's embarrassing.
also
Yasumori-san's
Hey, I'd like to put it in.
I want to put it in. Can I hear it one more time?
What? I forgot something.
Is that your best guess, Waka-chan?
Oh, no, I'm so embarrassed.
No, great good word.
You remember? Shin, are you all right?
well
That's what I'm talking about.
Here.
So it sounds like what he's talking about.
This kid says.
No? Isn't that what this is about?
That's what I thought I was seeing.
No?
That's what I thought.
My Happiness
I leave you with those words.
In his body, right?
He said he was going on a trip.
Great.
Can I hold that for you?
What kind of image do you have in your mind?
Can I ask you to say something?
In my opinion.
Since it is April.
Under new encounters
Go this pinguinj
With a touch of sadness.
I don't look back anymore.
That's what I meant.
It's all in there.
With that emotion.
Can I have it?
on one's way around
This is
I want a Waka-chan version too.
firm (not viscous or easily moved)
Of course.
that is
Because it is.
The first one to make it up.
Last I said.
He said this is the right thing to do.
the worst
I'm glad I read it.
This is going to be a great shot.
Don't get too many shots.
If you tell me.
I'm not a fan of the word "photographed".
Let's go to Shinji-san for once.
I'm a little bit happy.
I have a feeling for the future.
Positive.
Yes, I'll go.
My happiness was brought to me by my sea friends.
Can I look at the camera and smile? Oh no, I'm looking sideways a little now.
Noisy! ANNOYING!
You two ready?
Yes, sir.
Yes, then I'll say it's finished.
That was great.
Let's present the completed proposal!
Yes, sir.
Then I would like to start with the reverse side.
Here's a rough table of configurations.
Here is the logo of this aquarium
Name here
Illustration here
Great.
The name is cute in this hiragana font in
Good.
Well, good for all of us.
They even included our MC's.
Shimada-san is the only one who feels it.
I'd like to pull this off initially.
Good.
I'm looking forward to it.
You're out of your league.
Who's out of your league?
I didn't write that much.
Next, illustration by
Area below illustration
All right.
lovely
penguin gun
very cute
This is a quote from Yasumori.
Yes, sir.
I'd like a calendar of Yasumori's quotes.
I don't want to.
Japanese Calendar
Don't go ahead and talk.
Actually, it's full of them.
I'm sure it's in the drawer here.
Famous quotes are Yasumori's.
I know you're a first-rate guy.
Okay, this is good.
Please include a penguin gun.
cute
Cute and very good illustrations!
Well, here's what it looks like.
You don't have to write big.
And sleeves.
Ryoshen and the 95th Anniversaries too.
Shoulder.
crawl into (e.g. a hole)
red-breasted mogul (Mytilus galloprovincialis)
Animersary logo
Yes, please.
Wonderful.
This is wonderful.
great
Very nice.
I'm looking forward to the history.
This is the back side, or rather, the back.
Yes, sir.
And Yasumori
Yes I was in charge of the previous design.
Draw illustrations of the members.
I made it look like I was wearing a dolphin headdress.
First of all, this is Rune and Rinne.
cute
It's so cute!
I can't tell if it's a proper princess cut.
so many, many, many
While capturing facial features
From the members
yeah, yeah (used for casual, half-hearted, or insincere agreement)
Yunawa-kan is next.
hmm
Like this.
be known
Great.
I know that line.
Pearl Lotus Doll Vase in
hello (on phone, replying to "moshimoshi")
It looks like this.
The last one is Miyu Kayo.
cute
I'd like to see them laid out here like this.
The numbers are numbered in the order of their numbers.
in a nutshell
How big will it be?
It could be quite present.
hello (on phone, replying to "moshimoshi")
certainly
The bigger the better.
I'm a little hungry.
About this much.
But it could be cute.
Yes, sir.
I would like to see the design done in line with the
This is crazy good.
Like this.
Really nice.
used after the name of someone who is an older sister figure
Enough to make merchandise other than T-shirts.
branch of a sacred tree (esp. sakaki) with paper or cotton stripes
Hey, really.
happy
lovely
even... (e.g. "even a genius...")
Yes, that's really as good as it gets.
(after a noun) used when calling out to someone
Yes, sir.
happy
In fact, there will be some of these high tables in the future.
yeah
this (indicating an item near the speaker, the action of the speaker, or the current topic)
that is
Overwritten book tamako ni Zhang més捨
HAVE YOU
correct
that's so, isn't it
This time Clan On Number as the design Look
FW
why?
Idol SIleri to fulfillment.
oh, yes!
gems
(sentence end) indicates emphasis, agreement, request for confirmation, etc.
Yes, that's right, folks.
Suddenly Tohoku Aquarium, April 20 and 21, 2024
The event will be held at Sendai Umi-no-Mori Aquarium on the 20th and here at E-BEANS on the 21st.
I hope everyone will come and visit us and look forward to seeing the finished T-shirts.
Everyone is welcome to come and visit!
Let's make it a fun 2days!
yay
So, today's expedition was to come up with a T-shirt design!
Thank you very much.
That was fun!
yay